A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 2, Series 10 FA1448
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Center for Studying Health System Change - Cunningham (20060324), 2006-2009 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Ayanian (20060485), 2006-2008 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Regents of the University of California - Bindman (20060007), 2006-2008 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Muldoon (20080011), 2007-2008 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- President and Directors of Georgetown College - Summer (20070306), 2006-2009 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Altarum Institute - Hughes-Cromwick (20060304), 2006-2007 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Tufts-New England Medical Center - Perrin (20040124), 2003-2005 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- President and Directors of Georgetown College - Mayer (20040548), 2004-2007 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Cedars-Sinai Medical Center - Regalado, 1999-2007 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- The Century Foundation (20070347) - Future of the ESI Chartpack and Issue Brief (Box 117, Folder 5)
- The Century Foundation (20070347) - Lief Wellington Haase, 2007-2008 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Brandies University - Prottas (20040666), 2004-2006 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Australian-American Health Policy Fellowships 2004-2005 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20120193), 2011-2012 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- American College of Health Care Administrators - Tellis-Nayak (20050014), 2004-2005 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- State of California Department of Health Services - Rosenstein (20060535), 2006-2007 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- State of California Department of Health Services - Rosenstein (20060535) - Proposal Development, 2005-2006 (Box 118, Folder 7)
- Quality Partners of Rhode Island - Besdine (20060687, 20070013), 2006-2008 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Academic Pediatric Association - Minkovitz (20090603), 2009-2010 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Ayarian (20070775), 2007-2010 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20090260) - 2009 Policy Breakfast (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Trustees of Columbia University (20120023) - Sampat, 2011-2013 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- President and Directors of Georgetown University - Kofman (20120043), 2011-2013 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- The Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20110063), 2010-2011 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Simpson (20110476), 2011-2012 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Small Business Majority Foundation - Gardiner (20110222), 2010-2012 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20110340) (Box 120, Folder 4)
- National Opinion Research Center - Gabel (20110201), 2010-2012 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Children's Hospital Medical Center - Simpson (20070435) (Box 120, Folder 6)
- The Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20080400), 2008-2010 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20100609) - Health Insurance Survey, 2009-2011 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- The Lewin Group, Inc. - Sheils (20080401), 2008-2009 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Health Care Bills - Quality and Efficiency Bills Report, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Health Care Bills - Coverage Bills Report, 2009 January (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Health Care Bills - Bills Report - Revisions, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Health Care Bills - Bill Modeling and Summaries, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Affordable Health Insurance - Program Plan, 2009 March (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. (20080389) - International Survey of Primary Care Doctors, 2008-2010 (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. (20060276) - Strategic Health Perspectives, 2005-2006 (Box 122, Folder 3-4)
- The Massachusetts Health Quality Partners - Singer (20060112), 2004-2007 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Massachusetts Health Quality Partners - Singer (20060112) - Measuring and Reporting on the Quality and Resource Use of Massachusetts Physicians (Box 123, Folder 1-2)
- National Public Health and Hospital Institute - Cummings (20080031) - Final Report - Safety Net Hospitals and Emergency Department Throughput: Best Practices from High Performers (Box 123, Folder 3)
- International Communications Research, Inc. - Herrmann (20080430) - Rite of Passage (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Education and Research Fund of the Employee Benefit Research Institute - Frostin (20070463) - 2007 EBRI Consumerism Survey (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Education and Research Fund of the Employee Benefit Research Institute - Frostin (20060444) - EBRI 2006 Consumerism Survey (Box 124, Folder 1)
- The Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20070395) - Presidential Candidates Report, 2008 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- The Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20070395) - Presidential Candidates Health Proposals, 2008 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- International Communications Research, Inc. - Herrmann (20040176) - NASI - Older Adults Paper, 2005-2006 (Box 124, Folder 4)